Ibrahim Samadzada

LinkedIn | GitHub

Location: Azerbaijan, Baku Email: isamadzada@gmail.com | Mobile: +994558863884

FLUTTER DEVELOPER

As a passionate **Flutter developer** with over **2 year** experience, I am seeking opportunities to further develop my skills in this field. I am dedicated to expanding my knowledge and expertise in Flutter and am enthusiastic about the potential for growth in this area.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Languages : Dart, Java Script, Type Script : Flutter, React Native, Nest **Frameworks** Libraries : Bloc, Provider, Redux

Dev Tools : Visual Studio Code, Git, BitBucket, Gitlab

EXPERIENCE

FLutter-React Native Developer

Code and Care Remote - Wilmington, DE

- Developed dynamic, responsive and cross-platform mobile applications in a team using Flutter
- Worked with **REST APIs** to retrieve and display data from databases
- Worked on new features as Voice-memo and Image uploading

Flutter Developer

Aug 2022 - Jan 2023

Feb 2023 - Present

Digital Legion Full time – Azerbaijan, Baku

- Developed dynamic, responsive and cross-platform mobile applications as solo developer using Flutter
- Worked with REST APIs to retrieve and display data from databases
- Implemented Subscription and Payment system
- Implemented Chat system to let User write messages to Jasper AI

FLutter Developer

Jan 2022 - Aug 2022

Full time – Azerbaijan, Baku The Javachip

- Developed dynamic, responsive and cross-platform mobile applications as solo developer using Flutter
- Worked with REST APIs and WebSockets to retrieve and display data from databases
- Implemented **Pedometer logic** to track user's steps
- Implemented Real-time chat to let user's chat with each other

FLutter Developer

Jun 2021 - Jan 2022 Freelance Full time – Azerbaijan, Baku

• Worked on multiple projects as **solo** developer and **sometimes in team**.

EDUCATION

French-Azerbaijani University

Bachelor in Computer Science

Azerbaijan, Baku 2020 - 2024

Université de Strasbourg

France, Strasbourg 2020 - 2024

Bachelor in Computer Science

2Walk Flutter, Bloc Play Market

- Developed a clean and modern mobile application using Flutter
- Maintained business logic using **Bloc**
- Utilized **Responsive design** to ensure compatibility across all devices
- Implemented **Pedometer** to track user's steps

AlZodiac Flutter, Provider GitHub

- Developed a clean and modern mobile application using Flutter
- Maintained state management using **Provider**
- Utilized Responsive design to ensure compatibility across all devices
- Implemented Chat system to let User write messages to Jasper Al

LANGUAGES

Azerbaijani : Native language

Russian : Second Native

English : C1